[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "Is it as dangerous as it seems?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "as", "dangerous", "as", "it", "seems", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "The outcome still isn't clear.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "outcome", "still", "is", "n't", "clear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Are there enough people physically to do the job that's required?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "there", "enough", "people", "physically", "to", "do", "the", "job", "that", "'s", "required", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "They have no need to keep more people around than they absolutely need since all of them are soaking up dose.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "have", "no", "need", "to", "keep", "more", "people", "around", "than", "they", "absolutely", "need", "since", "all", "of", "them", "are", "soaking", "up", "dose", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chernobyl"]}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "How does this disaster compare -- this nuclear plant to something like Chernobyl?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "this", "disaster", "compare", "--", "this", "nuclear", "plant", "to", "something", "like", "Chernobyl", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "In Chernobyl, a completely different kind of reactor.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "Chernobyl", ",", "a", "completely", "different", "kind", "of", "reactor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "Without wanting to be doom-laden about this, but what is the worst possible news that you would hear as an expert in this area from that plant?", "question_tokens": ["Without", "wanting", "to", "be", "doom-laden", "about", "this", ",", "but", "what", "is", "the", "worst", "possible", "news", "that", "you", "would", "hear", "as", "an", "expert", "in", "this", "area", "from", "that", "plant", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "Probably that the spent fuel spool is on fire because what would burn there is the metal cladding, and that's very difficult to put out.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "that", "the", "spent", "fuel", "spool", "is", "on", "fire", "because", "what", "would", "burn", "there", "is", "the", "metal", "cladding", ",", "and", "that", "'s", "very", "difficult", "to", "put", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Why are you confident this is the right way to go?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "confident", "this", "is", "the", "right", "way", "to", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Well, the main thing I've said, Piers, is not that, but it's simply that it's way too early to know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "main", "thing", "I", "'ve", "said", ",", "Piers", ",", "is", "not", "that", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "simply", "that", "it", "'s", "way", "too", "early", "to", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "We've got lots of reactors, many by the sea?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "got", "lots", "of", "reactors", ",", "many", "by", "the", "sea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "What's going to happen if the same thing happens here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "going", "to", "happen", "if", "the", "same", "thing", "happens", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Piers, it's an obvious question.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "it", "'s", "an", "obvious", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Quite clearly, this is an ongoing, very serious and dangerous situation, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Quite", "clearly", ",", "this", "is", "an", "ongoing", ",", "very", "serious", "and", "dangerous", "situation", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "What are the lessons that we should learn from what's happened in regard to America's plants, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "lessons", "that", "we", "should", "learn", "from", "what", "'s", "happened", "in", "regard", "to", "America", "'s", "plants", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Piers, I have no earthly idea.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "have", "no", "earthly", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Isn't that the point?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "the", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "I think it would -- I think it would be irresponsible to do otherwise.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "would", "--", "I", "think", "it", "would", "be", "irresponsible", "to", "do", "otherwise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["Fukushima"]}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", ":", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Today the energy secretary, Stephen Chu, said that U.S. reactors are designed to withstand hurricanes and tsunamis, but given geologists' maximum predictions, is that actually enough?", "question_tokens": ["Today", "the", "energy", "secretary", ",", "Stephen", "Chu", ",", "said", "that", "U.S.", "reactors", "are", "designed", "to", "withstand", "hurricanes", "and", "tsunamis", ",", "but", "given", "geologists", "'", "maximum", "predictions", ",", "is", "that", "actually", "enough", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBN", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Well, Piers, I fully agree that there are important lessons to be learned by -- from what has happened at Fukushima.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "fully", "agree", "that", "there", "are", "important", "lessons", "to", "be", "learned", "by", "--", "from", "what", "has", "happened", "at", "Fukushima", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stephen Chu"], "LOCATION": ["U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan"]}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "As things stand given your knowledge of the nuclear power plants in America, how many of them would you think are able to withstands an earthquake of a magnitude we saw in Japan?", "question_tokens": ["As", "things", "stand", "given", "your", "knowledge", "of", "the", "nuclear", "power", "plants", "in", "America", ",", "how", "many", "of", "them", "would", "you", "think", "are", "able", "to", "withstands", "an", "earthquake", "of", "a", "magnitude", "we", "saw", "in", "Japan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "Well, let's remember that the reactors in Japan were quite old.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "'s", "remember", "that", "the", "reactors", "in", "Japan", "were", "quite", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Japan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Wouldn't that be the first point of thumb that you'd choose?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "that", "be", "the", "first", "point", "of", "thumb", "that", "you", "'d", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Well, the problem with that is that you'd end up building a reactor in a zone that is not subject to earthquakes to withstand an enormous earthquake.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "problem", "with", "that", "is", "that", "you", "'d", "end", "up", "building", "a", "reactor", "in", "a", "zone", "that", "is", "not", "subject", "to", "earthquakes", "to", "withstand", "an", "enormous", "earthquake", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Finally, Ambassador Ritch, do you think we're getting the truth out of the Japanese authorities?", "question_tokens": ["Finally", ",", "Ambassador", "Ritch", ",", "do", "you", "think", "we", "'re", "getting", "the", "truth", "out", "of", "the", "Japanese", "authorities", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "I do, but Piers, lets me make a point.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", ",", "but", "Piers", ",", "lets", "me", "make", "a", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ritch"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "For people like most of us who've never been anywhere near a tsunami, what is the experience like when it happens?", "question_tokens": ["For", "people", "like", "most", "of", "us", "who", "'ve", "never", "been", "anywhere", "near", "a", "tsunami", ",", "what", "is", "the", "experience", "like", "when", "it", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "WP", "-NONE-", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "The experience is just horrifying because you feel so powerless with the amount of power of the water.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "experience", "is", "just", "horrifying", "because", "you", "feel", "so", "powerless", "with", "the", "amount", "of", "power", "of", "the", "water", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "What is the most effective thing that Americans can do to help?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "most", "effective", "thing", "that", "Americans", "can", "do", "to", "help", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "On the level of helping children, the best way for them to recover and start healing process is to go back to normalcy, to go back to school, which is safe.", "answer_tokens": ["On", "the", "level", "of", "helping", "children", ",", "the", "best", "way", "for", "them", "to", "recover", "and", "start", "healing", "process", "is", "to", "go", "back", "to", "normalcy", ",", "to", "go", "back", "to", "school", ",", "which", "is", "safe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Do you still have nightmares about it now?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "have", "nightmares", "about", "it", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "You always will keep it inside.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "always", "will", "keep", "it", "inside", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "And finally, what would your message be to the people of Japan who are suffering so badly at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["And", "finally", ",", "what", "would", "your", "message", "be", "to", "the", "people", "of", "Japan", "who", "are", "suffering", "so", "badly", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "The message for them is that my heart is breaking looking at what they are going through.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "message", "for", "them", "is", "that", "my", "heart", "is", "breaking", "looking", "at", "what", "they", "are", "going", "through", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "How are they going to bounce back?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "they", "going", "to", "bounce", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "With time, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["With", "time", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "What will that mean for prices, in terms of their exports going forward?", "question_tokens": ["What", "will", "that", "mean", "for", "prices", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "their", "exports", "going", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Think of it in terms of they are producing and consuming less as a society.", "answer_tokens": ["Think", "of", "it", "in", "terms", "of", "they", "are", "producing", "and", "consuming", "less", "as", "a", "society", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Is that going to be helpful to Japan, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "going", "to", "be", "helpful", "to", "Japan", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "It's going to be helpful at the margin.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "helpful", "at", "the", "margin", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "What is it about the Japanese people that allows them to deal with such catastrophe in what appears to be such a remarkably calm manner?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "about", "the", "Japanese", "people", "that", "allows", "them", "to", "deal", "with", "such", "catastrophe", "in", "what", "appears", "to", "be", "such", "a", "remarkably", "calm", "manner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Well, I think that we in America -- when we come across a crisis, we tend to come apart at the seams.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "we", "in", "America", "--", "when", "we", "come", "across", "a", "crisis", ",", "we", "tend", "to", "come", "apart", "at", "the", "seams", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Are they very pro-active at getting things back on their feet again?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "very", "pro-active", "at", "getting", "things", "back", "on", "their", "feet", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "In general, Japanese officials leave one with kind of a sense of horror, I mean, just a difficult grappling with crisis.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "general", ",", "Japanese", "officials", "leave", "one", "with", "kind", "of", "a", "sense", "of", "horror", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "just", "a", "difficult", "grappling", "with", "crisis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Is that part of their psyche, as well?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "part", "of", "their", "psyche", ",", "as", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Do you still have friends over there?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "have", "friends", "over", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Oh, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Can you talk me through the relative toxicity of each of these?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "talk", "me", "through", "the", "relative", "toxicity", "of", "each", "of", "these", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Right, there are four different types of radiation, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "there", "are", "four", "different", "types", "of", "radiation", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "What is the understanding of the levels of radiation coming out of this Japanese plant?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "understanding", "of", "the", "levels", "of", "radiation", "coming", "out", "of", "this", "Japanese", "plant", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "We've been hearing that the levels of radiation are not quite at the level that you would see in order to have acute radiation sickness.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "been", "hearing", "that", "the", "levels", "of", "radiation", "are", "not", "quite", "at", "the", "level", "that", "you", "would", "see", "in", "order", "to", "have", "acute", "radiation", "sickness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "Tell me this, if they are exposed to very high dosages of radiation, what physically happens to a human being when that happens to them?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "this", ",", "if", "they", "are", "exposed", "to", "very", "high", "dosages", "of", "radiation", ",", "what", "physically", "happens", "to", "a", "human", "being", "when", "that", "happens", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "Right, it's interesting.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110315pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "And what are you hearing from Bahrain, where there seems to be an escalation in violence there, as well?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "are", "you", "hearing", "from", "Bahrain", ",", "where", "there", "seems", "to", "be", "an", "escalation", "in", "violence", "there", ",", "as", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "EX", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bahrain"]}}]